A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of Civilian Defense, 1940-1945.
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence, 1942-1945., Extent: 10.15 cubic feet (29 boxes). (Box 1-29)
  - Correspondence, 1942.
    - L - Miscellaneous, 1942 March-April. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - L - Miscellaneous, 1942January-February. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Landis, James M., Hon. (U.S. Office of Civilian Defense), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Lamb, William H. (Prince William County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Lancaster, Dabney S. (Superintendent of Public Instruction), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Landreth, S. F. (Galax CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Lane, H. M. (Campbell County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Larrick, H. R. (Clifton Forge CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Leap, William H. (American Red Cross), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Leap, C. C. (Waynesboro CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Ledman, Leamon (Prince William County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Lee, C. C. (Franklin County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Lee, J. Duval (Lynchburg CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Leigh, John P., Hon. (Portsmouth CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Lemley, G. M. (Frederick County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Lewis, Charles R. (Division of Purchase and Printing), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Lion Brothers Company, 1942. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Lippincott, H. S. (Newport News CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Logan, William H. (Shenandoah County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Loughborough, R. M. (Fairfax County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Lowe, W. H., Dr. (Lancaster County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Leubbert, C. H. (Virginia State Salvage Committee), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Luxford, Overton C., Maj. (Princess Anne County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1942 December. (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1942 November. (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1942 August. (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1942 July. (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1942 June. (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1942 May. (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1942 April. (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1942 March. (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1942 February. (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - M - Miscellaneous, 1942 January. (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - MacMillan, Theresa (Roanoke CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Mahaffey, S. J. (Henrico County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Mahon, Bernard (Caroline County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Mann, Charles H. (Arlington County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Marr, R. A., Col. (Virginia Military Institute), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Marshall, Richard M. (Norfolk CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Martin, Frank K. (Petersburg CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Marts, A. C., Dr. (Pennsylvania CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Marye, Burton, Jr. (Highway Traffic Advisory Committee), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Mason, Carson G. (Page County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Mason, Kate H., 1942. (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Massey, C. C. (Roanoke County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Mastin, Mary L. (Public Health Nursing), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Mathers, J. S. (Covington CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Mattern, E. K. (Roanoke County CDC), 1942. (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - McClosky, S. T., Maj. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - McDonnell, John C., Gen. (First Interceptor Command), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - McIntyre, W. T. (Staunton CDC), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - McRee, Fergus (Postmaster - Richmond), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - McWane, Fred (Lynchburg CDC), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Mead, William B. (Richmond Field Office), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Memoranda, 1942 October-November. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda, 1942 August-September. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Memoranda, 1942 June-July. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Memoranda, 1942 April-May. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Memoranda, 1942January-March. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda (Information), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda (Mr. Johnson), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda (J. Linwood Rice), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda (Transmittal), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Michael, R. D. (Blacksburg CDC), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Miles, Perry L. (Shenandoah Valley Regional Defense Council), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Mills, Virginia Kaye (Shenandoah Valley Regional Defense Council), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Miller, G. Tyler (Warren County CDC), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Miller, H. A., Jr. (Petersburg CDC), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Miller, Macon P. (Radford CDC), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Minter, W. M. (Mathews County CDC), 1942. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Modlin, Geroge M., Dr. (University of Richmond), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Moncure, Frank P. (Stafford County CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Moore, C. D. (Fries CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Moore, Stuart (Lexington CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Morris, B. M. (Richmond County CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Motz, W. C. (Nelson County CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Mullen, C. S. (Dept. of Highways), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - N - Miscellaneous, 1942November-December. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - N - Miscellaneous, 1942 September-October. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - N- Miscellaneous, 1942 July-August. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - N - Miscellaneous, 1942 May-June. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - N- Miscellaneous, 1942 March-April. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - N - Miscellaneous, 1942 January-February. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Neilson, George P., Jr. (Youth Activities Regional Representative), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Nelson, Robert (War Savings Staff), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Nufer, W. F. (North Carolina Council of National Defense), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - O - Miscellaneous, 1942. (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Owensm Arthur S. (Portsmouth CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - P - Miscellaneous, 1942 December. (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - P - Miscellaneous, 1942 November. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - P - Miscellaneous, 1942 September-October. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - P - Miscellaneous, 1942 July-August. (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - P - Miscellaneous, 1942 May-June. (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - P - Miscellaneous, 1942 March-April. (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - P - Miscellaneous, 1942 January-February. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Parks, Burton (U. S. Bureau of Industrial Conservation), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Patton, A. F. (Southern Piedmont Regional Defense Council), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Paulette, David W., Maj. (Virginia Defense Council), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Pederson, F. C. (Forest Fire Fighters Service), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Peebles, John K., Jr., 1942. (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Perkinson, Allan C., Maj. (Division of Aeronautics), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Pobst, Claude H. (Buchanan County CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Poff, J. H. (Floyd County CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Pomeroy, Hugh (State Planning Council), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Porter, A. O. (Marine Service Corps), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Price, A. H., Hon. (Wythe County CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Price, James H., Hon. (West Point CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Pulley, Junius W. (Southampton County CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Q - Miscellaneous, 1942. (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Quarles, Lawrence R. (University of Virginia), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Quirk, G. L. (Southern Piedmont Regional Defense Council), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - R - Miscellaneous, 1942 December. (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - R - Miscellaneous, 1942 November. (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - R - Miscellaneous, 1942 September-October. (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - R - Miscellaneous, 1942 August. (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - R - Miscellaneous, 1942 June-July. (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - R - Miscellanous, 1942 April-May. (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - R - Miscellaneous, 1942 March. (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - R - Miscellaneous, 1942 January-February. (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Radford, Duval (Bedford County CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Ragan, T. C. (Christiansburg CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Ramsey, Alma G. (Northern Virginia Regional Defense Council, 1942. (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Reckford, Milton A., Maj. Gen. (Third Service Command), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Reeves, Dache M., Col. (Air Corps - Langley Field), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Reninger, Henry A., Col. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Renkin, H. W. (Pocahontas CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Ricks, Helen (Extension Service, V.P.I.), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Riggin, I. C., Dr. (Emergency Medical Service), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Roberts, H. T. (Radford CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Roberts, Mills F., Jr. (South Norfolk CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Robertson, A. Stuart (Orange County CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Robertson, C. B. (Robertson Chemical Corporation), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Rodgers, R. L. (Rileyville CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Roebling, Parker, Mrs. (Luray CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Ross, Charles J. (Madison County CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Roudabush, R. E. (Shenandoah County CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Rowan, James H. (Halifax County CDC), 1942. (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - S - Miscellaneous, 1942 December. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - S - Miscellaneous, 1942 November. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - S - Miscellaneous, 1942 September-October. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - S - Miscellaneous, 1942 August. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - S - Miscellaneous, 1942 July. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - S - Miscellaneous, 1942 June. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - S - Miscellaneous, 1942 April-May. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - S- Miscellaneous, 1942 March. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - S - Miscellaneous, 1942 January-February. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Sale, E. A. (Martinsville CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Saunders, Edward W. (University of Virginia), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Saunders, S. B. (State Port Authority), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Scarff, John H. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Scott, Don E., Brig. Gen. (I.S.F. Virginia District), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Scott, Fred W. (U.S. Army - Procurement Branch), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Sears, Joseph D., Col. (War Department Civilian Protection School), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Sellew, R. W. (Third Service Command), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Shelburne, T. P. (Office of Price Administration), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Shepherd, Fred R. (Colonial Heights CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Simons, M. H., Rear Adm. (Fifth Naval District), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Simmons, James W. (Prince Edward County CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Sinclair, James W., Mrs., 1942. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Sipe, W. Edgar (Rockingham County CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Slemp, Wise, Mrs. (Big Stone Gap CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Sloane, George, Mrs., 1942. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Small, Sydney F. (Roanoke CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Smith, C. W. (Appomattox County CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Smith, E. Armstrong (Cumberland County CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Smith, J. Lawrence (Portsmouth CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Smithley, J. O., Maj. (Warwick County CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Snidow, W. S. (Christiansburg CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Spradlin, Ray H., Hon. (Mayor of Vinton), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Stallard, B. H. (St. Paul CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Stauffer, William H., Dr. (Commissioner of Public Welfare), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Steck, J. M. (Spotsylvania County CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Steele, R. E. (Coordinator of Railroads), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Stephenson, Harold (Fluvanna County CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Stewart, R. E. B. (Portsmouth CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Stewart, Malcolm N. (First Fighter Command), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Stoneburner, C. G. (Arlington County CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Stout, Lynn (Charlottesville CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Strudwick, E., Jr. (Air Raid Warning System), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Stuart, Charles E. (Westmoreland County CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Stuart, Walter P. (Saltville CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Sullivan, Willard, Mrs. (Hanover County CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Sunderland, A. H., Gen. (Elizabeth City CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Sutherland, E. J. (Dickenson County CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Sutherland, M. B. (Fries CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Sutton, David Nelson (West Point CDC), 1942. (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1942 December. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1942 November. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1942 September-October. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1942 August. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1942 July. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1942 June. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1942 April-May. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1942 March. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1942 January-February. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Tate, Mildred T., Dr. (Wise County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Tate, Vernon B. (Wise County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Taylor, George K. (Amelia County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Temple, E. G. (Greensville County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Thoma, Edward J. (Clarke County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Tiffany, Hunton (Prince William County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Todd, Bays M. (Grayson County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Tompkins, G. S. (American Viscose Corp.), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Tucker, Floyd W., Jr. (Hanover County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Turner, C. A., Rev. (York County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Turner, Horatio W. (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Turner, Lewis J. (Rappahannock County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Twitty, Evelyn (Petersburg CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Tyler, J. Alfred (Charles City County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Tynes, Finley (Shenandoah Valley Regional Defense Council), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - U - Miscellaneous, 1942. (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - V - Miscellaneous, 1942 November-December. (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - V - Miscellaneous, 1942 September-October. (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - V - Miscellaneous, 1942 July-August. (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - V - Miscellaneous, 1942 May-June. (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - V- Miscellaneous, 1942 March-April. (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - V - Miscellaneous, 1942 January-February. (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Van Dusseldorp, Wilma (Third Civilian Defense Regions), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Vass, I. G. (Waynesboro CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Vaughan, C. C. (Franklin CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Veech, J. A. (Lexington CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1942 December. (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1942 November. (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1942 October. (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1942 September. (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1942 August. (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1942 July. (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1942 June. (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1942 May. (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1942 April. (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1942 March. (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1942 February. (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1942 January. (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Wagner, Richard F. (Lynchburg Public Works), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Wailes, B. M., Mrs. (Sweet Briar), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Walker, H. M. (Northumberland County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Walker, L. M., Jr. (State Commissioner of Agriculture), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Walker, Robert B. (Fairfax County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Wallace, Maude E. (V. P. I. - Extension Service), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Waller, S. Garnder, Gen. (Adjutant General of Virginia), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Wardell, E. H. (Northumberland County CDC), 1942. (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Webb, H. L. (Greensville County CDC), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - West, R. John, Col. (Lynchburg CDC), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Wheeler, Frank H., Hon. (Clifton Forge CDC), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - White, Herman, Hon. (South Norfolk CDC), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - White, J. Horace (Russell County CDC), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Whitesell, S. M. (Fries CDC), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Will, J. E. (Luray CDC), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Williams, W. N. (Rockbridge County CDC), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Williams, William Page, Mrs. (Brookneal CDC), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Withrow, J. E. (Millboro CDC), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Wolfe, J. P., Jr. (Big Stone Gap CDC), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Woodbury, W. R. (Harrisonburg CDC), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Woodson, C. W., Maj. (Virginia State Police), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Worley, H. B. (Craig County CDC), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Wyse, J. H. (Office of Civilian Defense - Coordinator), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Y - Miscellaneous, 1942. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Z - Miscellaneous, 1942. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Zimmerman, Helen D. (Hampton Roads Regional Defense Council), 1942. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1943-1945.
    - A - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Abbitt, George, Jr. (Appomattox County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Abbitt, J. R. (Division of Grounds and Buildings), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Abeloff, Irvin G. (WRVA), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Abrams, S. C., Rev. (Fluvanna County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Ace Paper Company, 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Adams, Rowland K., Judge (Third Civilian Defense Region), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Addressograph Sales and Service Agency, 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Agnew, Ella G. (Virginia Child Care Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Alexander, Fred M., Dr. (Virginia High School Victory Corps), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Allen-Morrison Sign Company, 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Alles, George J. (Sylvania Industrical Corporation), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Alper, Saul (Wytheville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Ambler, Gordon B., Hon. (Richmond CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Amos, E. T. (Radford CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Ancell, W. Guy (Hopewell CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Anderson, C. R., Dr. (Winchester CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Anderson, J. A., Gen. (State Highway Dept.), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Anderson, James B., Lt. Col. (Norfolk Military Intelligence), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Anderson, R. N. (State Board of Education), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Ardinger, Markley (James City County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Arthur, R. William (Wythe County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Ayres, B. Drummond (Accomac County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Ayres, W. F. (Cape Charles CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Bab-Bay - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Bagley, I. T. (Blackstone CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Bain, W. W., Dr. (Nottoway County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Baker, W. L. (Covington CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Baltimore Transfer Company, 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Barclay, Elizabeth (Lexington CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Barkhouser, L. E. (Office of Price Administration), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Barlow, J. H. (Amonate CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Barnes, William C. (Martinsville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Barrett, Henry S. (Maryland Council of Defense), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Barton, Eugene A. (Third Civilian Defense Region Council), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Bassett, J. E. (Henry County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Baumes, Harold I. (League of Virginia Municipalities), 1943-1945. (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Bea-Bew - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Beckett, John H., Rev. (Princess Anne County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Bedwell, B. F. (Dinwiddie County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Bendheim, Sam (Neighborhood Theaters, Inc.), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Bennett, Joseph C. (Fairfax County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Bertram, George C. (Portsmouth CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Bethell, Mrs. Richard S. (Community War Service Division), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Bia-Bly - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Bickford, J. V., Mayor (Hampton, Emergency Coal Committee), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Biggins, J. C. (Newport News CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Binns, Mrs. J. S. (Charles City County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Bird, Paul E. (Smyth County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Birckhead, K. P. (Washington County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Birney, Harold (Solid Fuels Administration for War), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Bland, J. L., Hon. (West Point CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Bland, Lucille (West Point, Va.), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Blandford, Paul S. (Powhatan County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Blankenbaker, W. W. (Madison County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Boa-Boy - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Bobbitt, H. I. (Federal Bureau of Investigation), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Bolles, Lemuel, Col. (Protection Services Division - USOCD), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Bolton, R. J. (Montgomery County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Bonnstetter, G. A. (Protective Property Division - USOCD), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Booker, J. W. (Martinsville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Booth, A. A. (Danville CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Booth, W. A., Lt. Comm. (Middlesex County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Booth, Mrs. W. Harris (Middlesex County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Borden, G. W. (Frederick County), 1943-1945. (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Borland, Charles B. (Norfolk CDC), 1944-1945. (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Borland, Charles B. (Norfolk CDC), 1943. (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Bosang, J. G. (Pulaski County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Bourne, William C. (Office of War Information), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Bowman, John Fox (Fauquier County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Bra-Bry - Miscellaneous, 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Brabble, J. E., Professor (Norfolk County CDC), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Bradford, J. H. (Director of Personnel - State Capitol), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Brantly, E. C. (Conserve Critical Resources), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Bright, J. Fulmer, Brig. Gen. (Office of Price Administration), 1943-1945. (Box 16, Folder 8)